[
    {
        "question": "Ashraful should have said nothing",
        "words": {
          "4": "Ashraful",
          "1": "have",
          "3": "said",
          "2": "nothing",
          "5": "been",
          "6": "having",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "should",
          "9": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,1,5,3,7,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The killer may have killed many innocent people by now",
        "words": {
          "4": "innocent",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "killer",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "now",
          "6": "many",
          "7": "may",
          "8": "by",
          "9": "being",
          "10": "have",
          "11": "now",
          "12": "killed",
          "13": "people",
          "14": "the"
        },
        "answers":[[6,4,13,7,10,1,12,2,14,3,8,5],[6,4,13,7,10,1,12,8,14,3,2,5]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The referee will have finished the match by then",
        "words": {
          "4": "finished",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "the referee",
          "2": "then",
          "5": "the match",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "by",
          "8": "have",
          "9": "by",
          "10": "will",
          "11": "finish",
          "12": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[5,10,8,1,4,9,3,7,2],[5,10,8,1,4,7,3,9,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lalita loves to play table tennis",
        "words": {
          "4": "Lalita",
          "1": "played",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "table tennis",
          "5": "be",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "is",
          "8": "loved",
          "9": "playing"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,8,3,5,1,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I am planning to buy a new house",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "to",
          "3": "is",
          "2": "planned",
          "5": "bought",
          "6": "a",
          "7": "been",
          "8": "new",
          "9": "buy",
          "10": "being",
          "11": "by",
          "12": "house",
          "13": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[6,8,12,3,10,2,1,13,5,11,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shyam has learnt to cook fish",
        "words": {
          "4": "learnt",
          "1": "has",
          "3": "Shyam",
          "2": "cooking",
          "5": "been",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "being",
          "8": "fish"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,1,5,4,6,3]]
    },
    {
        "question": "You need to sing a song",
        "words": {
          "4": "singed",
          "1": "is",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "by",
          "5": "a",
          "6": "needed",
          "7": "sung",
          "8": "needs",
          "9": "be",
          "10": "song",
          "11": "you"
        },
        "answers":[[5,10,1,6,3,9,7,2,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "You have to play the game to win it",
        "words": {
          "4": "game",
          "1": "to be",
          "3": "won",
          "2": "played",
          "5": "has",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "to be",
          "8": "you",
          "9": "win",
          "10": "by"
        },
        "answers":[[6,4,5,7,2,1,3,10,8],[6,4,5,1,2,7,3,10,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "My book has been stolen",
        "words": {
          "4": "book",
          "1": "stolen",
          "3": "somebody",
          "2": "stole",
          "5": "my",
          "6": "has"
        },
        "answers":[[3,6,1,5,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Idrish was invited to the party",
        "words": {
          "4": "party",
          "1": "to",
          "3": "Idrish",
          "2": "someone",
          "5": "by",
          "6": "the",
          "7": "invited"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,3,1,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "I was asked my name",
        "words": {
          "4": "my",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "was",
          "2": "name",
          "5": "they",
          "6": "by",
          "7": "asked"
        },
        "answers":[[5,7,1,4,2]]
    }
]